<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>opinion on GKMNGRGN</title>
    <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/tags/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in opinion on GKMNGRGN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 15:24:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gokmengorgen.net/tags/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Review on My iPad</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/first-review-on-my-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 15:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/first-review-on-my-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I started using an iPad instead of a second laptop for more effective use. Although it is excellent for reading things, answering emails, checking tasks, it is still not possible to use as a laptop with these devices.
So I tried to connect to my primary PC remotely. But this was not satisfactory for me either. I took some notes to compare when iOS 13 and some updates came.
Pros  In tablet mode, all screens are full-sized automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 20:53:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/consumer/</guid>
      <description>For good things in life, you need labour, patience, and time.
 To draw a picture, To play an instrument, To program software, Or to produce something, Even to complete a book, To translate a text, To tell the troubles, To write what you think, To prepare a broadcast, For everything.  Just sharing something in social media and consuming it is easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What age do we live?</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/what-age-do-we-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 23:47:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/what-age-do-we-live/</guid>
      <description> Our technology is not so advanced to be an eye or an ear for us.
Or we&amp;rsquo;re not in an age where we don&amp;rsquo;t need our body yet.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spreadsheet applications</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/spreasheet-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 17:30:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/spreasheet-apps/</guid>
      <description>Spreadsheet applications are the most functional applications I&amp;rsquo;ve used. Excel, Gnumeric, Google Sheet, OpenOffice Calc or whatever, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. You can use it as task management like Trello, make daily - weekly - monthly plans, store and transfer data, and follow your financial situation. It&amp;rsquo;s like a Swiss army knife and not a new invention.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update this article when I find a more functional application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
