<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on GKMNGRGN</title>
    <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on GKMNGRGN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 22:44:15 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Default Fonts Problem on Firefox</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/05/how-to-fix-default-fonts-problem-on-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 22:44:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/05/how-to-fix-default-fonts-problem-on-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Most of the websites are using Helvetica as an alternative font, and Ubuntu is trying to set Nimbus Sans as a similar font even you have Helvetica font. Also, the default font on Firefox is DejaVu Sans, but the default fonts are working just if the styles don&amp;rsquo;t specify a font family in a website.

Nimbus Sans comes with fonts-urw-base35 package, and it&amp;rsquo;s ubuntu-desktop&amp;rsquo;s dependency, direct or indirect. I need ubuntu-desktop to use GNOME, so the best solution here is to disable the font altogether and refresh the fonts cache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rust Essentials</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/02/rust-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 22:22:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/02/rust-essentials/</guid>
      <description>Mostly I do not prefer to read the books written for teaching a programming language. Because a good language community already places the importance on their websites to promote the programming language beautifully as in Python and Rust. In these websites, you can find documentation, tutorials, even a free ebook that allows you to read from the website directly, and they&amp;rsquo;re mostly up-to-date.
As you know, Rust is not an easy-to-learn programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oceanhorn 2</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/02/oceanhorn2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 19:43:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/02/oceanhorn2/</guid>
      <description>I had trouble understanding the story of the game because I didn&amp;rsquo;t play the first one. You start to play the game in the middle of the adventure. You have a sword and shield, so you think that the story is in the past, but you also have a kind of motorcycle that has no wheels but can fly. Also, you have a brother in arms named Gen, and it&amp;rsquo;s a robot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inmost</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/01/inmost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 23:47:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2020/01/inmost/</guid>
      <description>I have a gaming PC for two years but couldn&amp;rsquo;t have time to play a game. So I decided to change my priorities in my life and will try to play more games and read more books this year.
My first plan was to play this game with my daughter, but I realized that it was not a suitable game for kids after I bought it, so I&amp;rsquo;ll pay attention to use the family filter from now on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being a Polyglot Developer</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/12/being-a-polyglot-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 13:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/12/being-a-polyglot-developer/</guid>
      <description>My objective for the year 2019 was joining one more programming language community after Python and Lisp. I followed .NET Core in my first six months and did some projects using C# and F#. But then, I decided that learning Rust is a better idea. Some of the Python and Django developers I&amp;rsquo;ve followed have had a significant impact on my decision.
Python is a programming language that easy to learn, it has a significant and active community, and I believe that it will keep its popularity for a longer time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Types in Programming</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/data-types-in-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 01:04:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/data-types-in-programming/</guid>
      <description>I started to take a look at C++ courses to understand Rust better because it helps me to see the advantages of Rust. The following images are from a Linkedin course, the instructor is Bill Weinman, and his courses are perfect if you want to program with C++.
If you have a photographic memory to remind something quickly, then you may like these images explaining data types in programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Review on My iPad</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/first-review-on-my-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 15:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/08/first-review-on-my-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I started using an iPad instead of a second laptop for more effective use. Although it is excellent for reading things, answering emails, checking tasks, it is still not possible to use as a laptop with these devices.
So I tried to connect to my primary PC remotely. But this was not satisfactory for me either. I took some notes to compare when iOS 13 and some updates came.
Pros  In tablet mode, all screens are full-sized automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Wrong After The Vacation</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/06/my-first-wrong-after-the-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 13:33:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/06/my-first-wrong-after-the-vacation/</guid>
      <description>At the end of my three-week vacation, I was asked for a seemingly easy task. We were going to release the new version of the project we developed:
 Is today is the last working of the week? No. Is there any problem with the unit tests? No. Are all changes confirmed by the product manager, in the staging server? Yes.  I always note everything, and so I write this article to remind this experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Windows for Development</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/03/configure-windows-for-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 19:35:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/03/configure-windows-for-development/</guid>
      <description>Environment Variables I still use some development tools that are used by most Linux users and these tools need some environment variables like LC_ALL, HOME, etc. When I have a new PC with Windows 10, I start to use with defining these variables. Take a look at this post for more detail.
PowerShell Core It&amp;rsquo;s possible to use BASH on Windows indeed, but I think PowerShell Core is a good alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 20:53:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/consumer/</guid>
      <description>For good things in life, you need labour, patience, and time.
 To draw a picture, To play an instrument, To program software, Or to produce something, Even to complete a book, To translate a text, To tell the troubles, To write what you think, To prepare a broadcast, For everything.  Just sharing something in social media and consuming it is easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What age do we live?</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/what-age-do-we-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 23:47:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/02/what-age-do-we-live/</guid>
      <description> Our technology is not so advanced to be an eye or an ear for us.
Or we&amp;rsquo;re not in an age where we don&amp;rsquo;t need our body yet.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>String quotes in PEP8</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/string-quotes-in-pep8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 23:59:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/string-quotes-in-pep8/</guid>
      <description>I use PEP8 in my Python projects except for a few rules.
I think &amp;lsquo;single-quote&amp;rsquo; and &amp;ldquo;double-quote&amp;rdquo; characters should NOT be the same. It could be better if these two characters had different counterparts in the Python language parser system. So we could use one of them for the template-strings (or f-strings). It doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide readability, causes inconsistency instead. Until now, I used string-quotes for the variable definitions and double-quotes for the visible texts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spreadsheet applications</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/spreasheet-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 17:30:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2019/01/spreasheet-apps/</guid>
      <description>Spreadsheet applications are the most functional applications I&amp;rsquo;ve used. Excel, Gnumeric, Google Sheet, OpenOffice Calc or whatever, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. You can use it as task management like Trello, make daily - weekly - monthly plans, store and transfer data, and follow your financial situation. It&amp;rsquo;s like a Swiss army knife and not a new invention.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update this article when I find a more functional application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I publish my articles?</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2018/12/how-do-i-publish-my-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 15:06:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2018/12/how-do-i-publish-my-articles/</guid>
      <description>With just a command:
# terminal $ ENV=PROD ./do.sh deploy I have many projects using my script named DOSH and the parameters are mostly in common; deploy, start, stop, runtests, etc. It can be a .NET Core or a Django project, or just a website using any static site generator like this one but I run all the projects with the same command: dosh start.
In Windows, the command may be a bit longer than in the other operating systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Windows Environment Variables</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2018/12/important-windows-environment-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 21:25:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/blog/2018/12/important-windows-environment-variables/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell and Git encoding problems To make git log command output properly display on Windows, we need to set a variable named LC_ALL:
LC_ALL=&amp;#34;C.UTF-8&amp;#34; Incorrect home folder in Emacs This problem is not only about Emacs. If you try to find a file from HOME variable, you may need to define the variable first:
HOME=&amp;#34;%USERPROFILE%&amp;#34; ;; place all backup files in one directory (setq backup-directory-alist `((&amp;#34;.*&amp;#34; . ,temporary-file-directory))) (setq auto-save-file-name-transforms `((&amp;#34;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
