<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on GKMNGRGN</title>
    <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on GKMNGRGN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 23:47:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What age do we live?</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/what-age-do-we-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 23:47:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/what-age-do-we-live/</guid>
      <description> Our technology is not so advanced to be an eye or an ear for us.
Or we&amp;rsquo;re not in an age where we don&amp;rsquo;t need our body yet.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>String quotes in PEP8</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/string-quotes-in-pep8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 23:59:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/string-quotes-in-pep8/</guid>
      <description>I use PEP8 in my Python projects except for a few rules.
I think &amp;lsquo;single-quote&amp;rsquo; and &amp;ldquo;double-quote&amp;rdquo; characters should NOT be the same. It could be better if these two characters had different counterparts in the Python language parser system. So we could use one of them for the template-strings (or f-strings). It doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide readability, causes inconsistency instead. Until now, I used string-quotes for the variable definitions and double-quotes for the visible texts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spreadsheet applications</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/spreasheet-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 17:30:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/spreasheet-apps/</guid>
      <description>Spreadsheet applications are the most functional applications I&amp;rsquo;ve used. Excel, Gnumeric, Google Sheet, OpenOffice Calc or whatever, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. You can use it as task management like Trello, make daily - weekly - monthly plans, store and transfer data, and follow your financial situation. It&amp;rsquo;s like a Swiss army knife and not a new invention.
I&amp;rsquo;ll update this article when I find a more functional application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I publish my articles?</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/how-do-i-publish-my-articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 15:06:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/how-do-i-publish-my-articles/</guid>
      <description>With just a command:
# terminal $ ENV=PROD ./do.sh deploy  I have many projects using my script named DOSH and the parameters are mostly in common; deploy, start, stop, runtests, etc. It can be a .NET Core or a Django project, or just a website using any static site generator like this one but I run all the projects with the same command: dosh start.
In Windows, the command may be a bit longer than in the other operating systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Windows environment variables</title>
      <link>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/important-windows-environment-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 21:25:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gokmengorgen.net/en/blog/important-windows-environment-variables/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell and Git encoding problems To make git log command output properly display on Windows, we need to set a variable named LC_ALL:
LC_ALL=&amp;quot;C.UTF-8&amp;quot;  Incorrect home folder in Emacs This problem is not only about Emacs. If you try to find a file from HOME variable, you may need to define the variable first:
HOME=&amp;quot;%USERPROFILE%&amp;quot;  ;; place all backup files in one directory (setq backup-directory-alist `((&amp;quot;.*&amp;quot; . ,temporary-file-directory))) (setq auto-save-file-name-transforms `((&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>